We're going to need you all today, April 5th, and we're going to love you, and if you'd like us to come back to us the other weeks.
The other day, I thank you for this beautiful season.
Whether it's in the heat, if people don't honor tonight, for the seasons that will be made,
I'm afraid that you'd bless the most of those decisions you've ever used to.
And Father, I thank you for your love.
We think about it a lot in history.
And how you did it, which you did.
Father, I think also the way you said that the power you took to raise him in the dead,
he would put in us.
So much of power, being in our people and making decisions.
Even with this, use it even tonight.
You should just say, look, we're ready.
Have plenty of patience to live at the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which you're saying,
one nation and another, in the list of the liberty and the rest of the world.
We're going to want to pull more public input and we'll say it for all three of us.
Except in the right way to the group.
Five, six, three, eight.
So much.
Two, five.
Nine.
Except for deck holes in the associate's work order number 20.
We're going to bring that student for a place in the paper.
We're in structure.
They see this for about a time.
So I'm counting.
Yes, sir.
So this is for, I've also been designed to actually fit out.
If you notice the money go over 125, you'll get there in the playground.
At the age train structures.
It's been a lot of time and quarter.
So we're going to replace those actually when I'm broken.
You can't go anywhere.
We're going to replace those in the steel structures that are made to just
Dan and water through the desert.
The real idea is to just in a lot of water.
And that sort of place all that.
I mean.
So that's for that.
This will work for them to do that.
So.
For sure.
I mean more flood troops.
Because I mean that piece.
Everybody in the southwest.
We have another way to be to see which is another work order.
But just.
I think that's.
It's.
Yes, sir.
only at one minute, sir.
What?
What is state local?
calculate 7 or a decade old, to associate 4 or 241ho2.
The history, the heater on the position of the design.
The project in the background is local, the sample, the southeast, and east, the B-عدage.
So this is actually going from the Trenstructures all the way back to the subsidization.
So I think I have the only substitute there, plus the deductible.
So now we're going to replace the metal feeder line.
So this part of our capital is going to probably be the other project that we had.
So we'll be replacing all of that.
So this is essentially the,
yes, for the operations, for the protection end of out of there,
and to be done, because they all look different.
If it's anything about it, you want to borrow those lines.
So there's a personal line on that.
So I mean, something to get a lot of questions about.
So basically, why do you guys know that black stuff,
or the crazy stuff on the new boat?
So that's greater to our key to that actual world.
There's a key to that, but we don't know what kind of things they've done.
So I think it's a lot of that at the same time.
We'll see if we can keep that to the current.
So, second.
Okay.
Second.
Next.
It is also down there and I agree that there was a lot and if you've ever been down to the old,
not a stressful rate, so we have to have this door on the right comment.
I'm going to power on direct there, too, so we want to press all the bolts in.
If we ever have a app, if we have a full of breaks down in there, there's a flood of pain on me.
So this is south of the early park.
Yes, there's wood.
Yeah, back home with back in there.
Oh, we do.
We go down that other day.
That means we're down the right.
We're still with.
We have no permission.
I make the motion that we need to.
Second.
We'll have to.
I need some bolts.
All of it.
Thank you.
Well, I'll leave it to this neighbor since we close to the student.
We're doing trustee community practice.
14 gentlemen.
So.
Second.
Two.
Four.
One.